This is Archaon the Everchosen,
Ruler of the Warriors of Chaos and so evil
he punches puppies.
Champion of the Chaos gods, he would bring in the end of times. Archaon destroyed cities,
butchered his enemies and ate them raw.
So he died of constipation.
The death of their supreme leader ironically threw the warriors of Chaos into chaos.
It was also irritating the gods of Chaos,
as ending the world was quickly reaching its deadline.
In a fit of anger, Ko'orn,
God of Body Fluids,
shouted to the warriors, "Might as well make that guy Everchosen."
This is Melvin.
[DING]
He used to make horseshoes,
and now he's going to bring in the apocalypse.
The problem was that no one wanted to follow him.
Chaos Warriors are loyal to savage, brutal warriors
and Melvin had only defeated a mosquito.
So he tried to get everyone to like him by making them garlic bread.
Warriors hate garlic bread.
Dragon ogres love it, and warriors love not getting stomped to death,
ensuring loyalty.
Before Melvin and his friends could invade the south,
he would need to become king of the savage Chaos worshipping tribes.
That bothered him.
Calling them tribes was so unprogressive
and he had a thought that would change everything.
"All of this Chaos business was very backwards
it was time to rebrand."
The Warriors of Chaos was no more.
They were now the Defence Force of Disorganization and promised the savage worshiping
*communities* good pay and career opportunities.
Most men signed up. There wasn't much else to do. Their first target was the Empire.
This is Karl
[DING]
A war loving emperor that put his empire in a state of Total War™.
Yes.
Very meta™.
When the Everchosen found out about this,
he was actually annoyed.
That was against everything he stood for.
He was gonna have a serious talk with this 'Karl'.
Humans were very ready for a Chaos attack.
The Empire's tax money was supposed to go to schools, roads, and uh,
the rest,
but because of fear-mongering, no one stopped Karl when he spent it all on medieval energy weapons.
Then Melvin showed up alone,
demanding a debate, and his support fell.
Collapsed. Karl won't leave this field alive.
Then like dominoes every human kingdom fell because they were only human
that had also spent all their money on medieval energy weapons.
Not wanting to get caught in the 100 civil wars, the warriors fled into the forest - home of the wood elves.
Much smarter than humans.
So Melvin knew he wouldn't luck out this time. He came up with the most convoluted,
advanced, and unrealistic plan.
He was gonna
- never get to execute it because while he was planning,
Zuldavaar the Butcher and
Simon were having a smoke break.
Wood elves do not test their smoke detectors.
They had to run out or choke to death and reached
Zombieland.
The Undeads were ruled by Manfred von Kahr Stein, a vampire obsessed with
inconvenient architecture and cutting skulls into mountains.
Immortal and bored, he recently spent all his money
resurrecting a skeleton,
who did not live up to the hype.
Now as the tumult corps arrived, he could not afford to fight them,
so he came up with an idea: invite Melvin to dinner and make him his minion.
Melvin agreed,
but forgot to ask what to bring, and to mention he was a vegetarian.
In the end he brought his favorite appetizer,
garlic bread.
The other vampires immediately told all forces that if they kill the Everchosen they would get power beyond their wildest dreams.
Melvin responded if they didn't kill him they would get milk.
With everyone fighting, he snuck out the back and ended up in the mountains by the kingdom of the dwarves.
Time to burn their stone cities.
Craniums for the cranium chair.
So they marched up the mountains.
Then they marched down the mountains.
It was very cold.
Melvin wondered:
Did he really have to take on the dwarves?
The Greenskins are way more disorganized than he ever was, can't they do it?
So he sent a polite letter.
"Dear Grimgor Ironhide,
We are having problems with
little persons in mountains.
Would be grateful for your help.
Love, Melvin"
The Greenskins responded: "Dear Melvin,
WAAAGH"
He wasn't sure if that was a no or a yes.
But the next day the Greenskins climbed the mountains.
Greenskins consist of the Orcs and their cowardly punching bags. With axes, arrows,
and moral support,
the dwarf capital was set aflame. To celebrate, Melvin offered the leaders some rosea wine, and
something happened when the cowardly Graknik for the first time tasted liquid courage.
[La Marseillaise, French National Anthem]
Wine had once again started a class war.
It said the piranha can turn a human into bones in a matter of minutes.
Goblins laugh at the piranhas.
Meanwhile in a conference room, the dark gods were arguing who should bring Chaos to the world
when they looked over their shoulder and noticed it had already happened.
With their chosen warriors not spilling a drop of blood.
The Chaos gods, as opposed to their names, are very strict and conservative.
This Melvin had brought Chaos, but not the Chaos they like. He had to die.
This is Tzeentch,
[DING]
the God of calculating and
birds.
To kill Melvin, he sent down a duck. But before he could kill him,
Tzeentch noticed something about the human that made the old god shed a tear.
This was the only mortal to not eat bird.
Tzeentch couldn't do it.
He'd rather kill the other gods than kill him, causing a God War™.
Melvin was very confused who *those* people were,
but it appeared he had done it. The world and other worlds were engulfed in
disorganization and everyone was killing each other. Yet,
there was a bigger victim than the millions of dead.
The farms that grew garlic and the farms that grew bread.
Without garlic's bowel healing power,
Melvin...
died of constipation.